Ambria Johnson

Contact: (678)613-0298 | 1223ambria@gmail.com | LinkedIn; www.linkedin.com/in/ambria-johnson23

OBJECTIVE

I am a recent college graduate from Howard University with a projected full-stack web development certificate from the Georgia Institute of Technology. I am a highly motivated individual, looking forward to being in a work environment that encourages innovation and professional growth. With a recent career shift from the healthcare industry to web development, I would like to implement a more efficient and user-friendly experience for customers and employees with technology.

EDUCATION

Howard University | Washington, DC

Bachelor of Science: Biology

Georgia Institute of Technology | Atlanta, Ga

Certification: TBA

Leadership

Breaking the Cycle Organization Howard Chapter

October 2017 – October 2020

Executive board member/PR & graphic designer

- Used my Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator skills to create the organizations logo and to create flyers for events
- Created and organized a daily planner for the organization's social media posts on Instagram and twitter platforms
- Co-managed with executive board members for future volunteer work and events

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

CVS Pharmacy | Atlanta, GA

November 2021 - Dec. 2022

Certified Pharmacy Technician

- Receiving and storing incoming inventory, verifying quantities against invoices, and checking for outdated medications.
- Performing trouble shooting for clients with insurance issues to resolve problems.
- Maintaining inventory levels, pulling outdated/recalled merchandise.
- Responsible customer service representative; Interacting with customers, receiving and verifying prescriptions and refills.

CVS Pharmacy | Chicago, IL

January 2019 - May 2021

Shift Supervisor (January 2019– May 2021)

- Responsible for assisting the store manager in maintaining a positive work environment, which provides efficient and welcoming service guaranteeing a complete quality experience for both the customers and employees.
- Delegated tasks among subordinate employees
- Assisted in employee training and performance management
- Maintained exceptional customer service
- Lead shifts which required completing store tasks and balancing out registers and store safe
- Accountable for recording technical aspects of store sales

Accomplishments:

- Recognized for initiating and finishing responsibilities throughout the store
- Received recognition for remarkable customer service
- Sold 70% above the quota for a CVS rewards program in one day

INTERNSHIP EXPERIENCE

Seattle Cancer Care Alliance | Seattle, Washington

June 2019 – July 2019

Shadowing oncologists specializing in different fields of oncology

Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center | Seattle, Washington

Researcher

June 2018 – August 2019

- Quickly learned laboratory skills such as pipetting, aliquoting, gel electrophoresis, and dissociating tissue cells
- Carefully researched with 40 samples of patient DNA for the presence of a particular gene
- Maintained two research projects focusing on Acute Myeloid Leukemia for eight weeks in two principal investigators labs
- Lead college discussions for high school interns at Fred Hutchinson
- Presented research results to established staff

Accomplishments

- Published research data generated from my research results
- Received Human Subjects in Bioethics Completion Certificate

College of Arts and Sciences Graphic Design Internship

- Created flyers for events regarding Howard University
- Learned basic features of Adobe Photoshop and Adobe Illustrator

August 2017 – October 2017

VOLUNTEER WORK

- Howard University Alternative Spring Break

 Volunteered in the Washington, DC area focusing on community issues such as homelessness, resources for job opportunities, food deserts, and mental health
 - Expanded upon teamwork skills through community service activities
 - Volunteered for specific community aspects around the Washington, DC area
 - Raised

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- APIs
- Nodejs
- SQL